DYLAN BARKOWSKY



dylanbarkowsky@gmail.com

780.237.5172

ABOUT ME

Detail-focused individual who thrives when presented with problems where the solution is not always clear. Experienced in working in project-orientated environments, communicating with coworkers and clients to achieve project goals. Aims to automate and innovate existing systems wherever possible.

SOFT SKILLS		TECHNICAL SKILLS	
Time Management	Problem Solving	MS Office	Azure & O365 Admin
Communication	Conflict Resolution	Docker	Web Development
Copyediting & Writing	Adaptability	CI/CD Process	Database Management

EDUCATION & CERTIFICATIONS

Information & Computer Systems Diploma

Camosun College Ongoing

Professional Certificate in Asset Management Planning

IPWEA & NAMS Canada 2020

CompTIA A+ Certification

CompTIA 2019

ITIL 4 Foundation

Axelos 2019

Bachelor of Arts (Hons) **Applied Linquistics**

University of Victoria 2013

REFERENCES

References available upon request.

EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

Full Stack Project Analyst

Ministry of Citizens' Services | Saanich, BC | 2022/05—2022/08

- Implemented testing framework to develop frontend and backend tests
- Created GitHub Actions workflows to automate testing, security scanning, and record results
- Containerized application to provide production-ready images as well as specialized images for portable developer environment

Engineering Assistant

City of Victoria | Victoria, BC | 2021/05—2021/09

- Collecting and maintaining data on traffic patterns
- Working with specialized software to analyse and report on data trends
- Installing and operating traffic-monitoring devices

Technical Assistant

City of Victoria | Victoria, BC | 2019/02—2020/12

- Creating spreadsheets, forms, documents, and graphical items
- Assessing and quantifying data of City assets
- Utilizing tools such as Office, SharePoint, and Power Platform to create project solutions

Adult Tutor

A&D Tutoring | Edmonton, AB | 2015/10—2017/06

- · Providing adults with education and job training
- Preparing one-on-one lessons and planning curricula
- Teaching the following subjects: ESL, Computers, Microsoft Office, GED, Math, English, Customer Service

EFL Instructor

HESS International | Qidu, Taiwan | 2014/07—2015/07

- Instructing students from ages 3-16 in English
- Planning lessons and applying existing curricula